Girl Power to the Rescue!
Barbie and the Three Musketeers is a animation,
family film directed by William Lau.
Corinne is a young country girl who heads to Paris to pursue
her big dream – to become a female musketeer!
Never could she imagine she would meet three other
girls who secretly share the same dream!
Using their special talents, the girls work together as a
team to foil a plot and save the prince.
It's all for one and one for all!
Barbie as Corrine (voice), played by Kelly Sheridan.
Philippe (voice), played by Tim Curry.
Viveca (voice), played by Kira Tozer.
Aramina (voice), played by Willow Johnson.
Renée (voice), played by Dorla Bell.
Corinne's Mother / Fancy Dress Girl #1 (voice), played by Nicole Oliver.
Barbie and the Three Musketeers is a 2009 animated fantasy film.
It was released to DVD on September 15, 2009, and made its
television premiere on Nickelodeon on November 22, 2009.
This film is the sixteenth entry in the Barbie film series.
It features the voice of Kelly Sheridan as Corinne d'Artagnan (played by Barbie) and
is based on the 1844 novel The Three Musketeers by Alexandre Dumas.
The film explores themes of female friendship, based on toy,
female protagonist, musketeer, 3d animation.